[{"task_id":1,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (-2 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"4","wrong_answer2":"3","wrong_answer3":"5","correct_answer":"2","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":2,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -4i \\cdot (-1 + i)?","wrong_answer1":"3","wrong_answer2":"1","wrong_answer3":"6","correct_answer":"4","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":3,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (1 - 8 i)?","wrong_answer1":"1","wrong_answer2":"2","wrong_answer3":"7","correct_answer":"4","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":4,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 1i \\cdot (1 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-1","wrong_answer2":"-2","wrong_answer3":"4","correct_answer":"1","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":5,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (5 - 4 i)?","wrong_answer1":"17","wrong_answer2":"19","wrong_answer3":"23","correct_answer":"20","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":6,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (-6 + 8 i)?","wrong_answer1":"27","wrong_answer2":"29","wrong_answer3":"33","correct_answer":"30","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":7,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (-1 + 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-2","wrong_answer2":"0","wrong_answer3":"-4","correct_answer":"-3","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":8,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 5i \\cdot (-1 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-4","wrong_answer2":"-3","wrong_answer3":"-8","correct_answer":"-5","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":9,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (-7 + 7 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-27","wrong_answer2":"-30","wrong_answer3":"-25","correct_answer":"-28","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":10,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (3 + 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-1","wrong_answer2":"-5","wrong_answer3":"-6","correct_answer":"-3","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":11,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 1i \\cdot (-3 - 5 i)?","wrong_answer1":"0","wrong_answer2":"-4","wrong_answer3":"-5","correct_answer":"-3","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":12,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 9i \\cdot (-4 + 8 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-34","wrong_answer2":"-39","wrong_answer3":"-33","correct_answer":"-36","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":13,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (3 + i)?","wrong_answer1":"-2","wrong_answer2":"0","wrong_answer3":"-4","correct_answer":"-3","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":14,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (-3 - 4 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-11","wrong_answer2":"-10","wrong_answer3":"-14","correct_answer":"-12","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":15,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (8 + 6 i)?","wrong_answer1":"17","wrong_answer2":"15","wrong_answer3":"18","correct_answer":"16","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":16,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-2 + 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-3","wrong_answer2":"-5","wrong_answer3":"-2","correct_answer":"-4","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":17,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-5 - 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-8","wrong_answer2":"-9","wrong_answer3":"-7","correct_answer":"-10","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":18,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 10i \\cdot (5 - 4 i)?","wrong_answer1":"47","wrong_answer2":"49","wrong_answer3":"52","correct_answer":"50","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":19,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-2 + 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-1","wrong_answer2":"-5","wrong_answer3":"-3","correct_answer":"-4","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":20,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-5 - 5 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-13","wrong_answer2":"-7","wrong_answer3":"-12","correct_answer":"-10","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":21,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -7i \\cdot (2 - i)?","wrong_answer1":"-16","wrong_answer2":"-12","wrong_answer3":"-17","correct_answer":"-14","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":22,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (1 + 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-1","wrong_answer2":"0","wrong_answer3":"1","correct_answer":"2","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":23,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 5i \\cdot (-1 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-8","wrong_answer2":"-3","wrong_answer3":"-6","correct_answer":"-5","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":24,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -2i \\cdot (3 + 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-5","wrong_answer2":"-8","wrong_answer3":"-9","correct_answer":"-6","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":25,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (3 + 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-12","wrong_answer2":"-8","wrong_answer3":"-6","correct_answer":"-9","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":26,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (4 - 4 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-6","wrong_answer2":"-7","wrong_answer3":"-3","correct_answer":"-4","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":27,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 1i \\cdot (5 - 8 i)?","wrong_answer1":"3","wrong_answer2":"8","wrong_answer3":"6","correct_answer":"5","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":28,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 1i \\cdot (-1 + 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"1","wrong_answer2":"-4","wrong_answer3":"2","correct_answer":"-1","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":29,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (-1 - 4 i)?","wrong_answer1":"3","wrong_answer2":"-2","wrong_answer3":"-1","correct_answer":"1","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":30,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -7i \\cdot (-8 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"59","wrong_answer2":"55","wrong_answer3":"53","correct_answer":"56","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":31,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -2i \\cdot (2 + 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-1","wrong_answer2":"-3","wrong_answer3":"-7","correct_answer":"-4","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":32,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (-1 - 4 i)?","wrong_answer1":"5","wrong_answer2":"1","wrong_answer3":"0","correct_answer":"3","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":33,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 7i \\cdot (4 + 9 i)?","wrong_answer1":"27","wrong_answer2":"31","wrong_answer3":"25","correct_answer":"28","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":34,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (3 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"8","wrong_answer2":"6","wrong_answer3":"7","correct_answer":"9","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":35,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (3 + 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"0","wrong_answer2":"-6","wrong_answer3":"-2","correct_answer":"-3","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":36,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 10i \\cdot (-1 + 4 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-9","wrong_answer2":"-11","wrong_answer3":"-13","correct_answer":"-10","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":37,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (2 - 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-5","wrong_answer2":"-4","wrong_answer3":"-3","correct_answer":"-6","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":38,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (1 + 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"0","wrong_answer2":"1","wrong_answer3":"6","correct_answer":"3","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":39,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (-8 + i)?","wrong_answer1":"-22","wrong_answer2":"-23","wrong_answer3":"-26","correct_answer":"-24","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":40,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (-1 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"5","wrong_answer2":"1","wrong_answer3":"4","correct_answer":"3","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":41,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (-2 + 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"8","wrong_answer2":"7","wrong_answer3":"11","correct_answer":"10","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":42,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (-5 + 10 i)?","wrong_answer1":"17","wrong_answer2":"13","wrong_answer3":"16","correct_answer":"15","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":43,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (3 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"12","wrong_answer2":"10","wrong_answer3":"11","correct_answer":"9","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":44,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 4i \\cdot (2 - 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"11","wrong_answer2":"7","wrong_answer3":"5","correct_answer":"8","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":45,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -4i \\cdot (5 + 5 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-22","wrong_answer2":"-18","wrong_answer3":"-19","correct_answer":"-20","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":46,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (-3 + 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-8","wrong_answer2":"-10","wrong_answer3":"-11","correct_answer":"-9","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":47,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (-1 + 5 i)?","wrong_answer1":"0","wrong_answer2":"-5","wrong_answer3":"-6","correct_answer":"-3","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":48,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 6i \\cdot (-4 - 5 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-21","wrong_answer2":"-23","wrong_answer3":"-27","correct_answer":"-24","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":49,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 3i \\cdot (2 - 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"7","wrong_answer2":"4","wrong_answer3":"9","correct_answer":"6","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":50,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (4 - 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-17","wrong_answer2":"-18","wrong_answer3":"-19","correct_answer":"-20","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":51,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (2 + 7 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-12","wrong_answer2":"-7","wrong_answer3":"-9","correct_answer":"-10","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":52,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (-1 - 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"4","wrong_answer2":"2","wrong_answer3":"-2","correct_answer":"1","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":53,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -5i \\cdot (-1 + i)?","wrong_answer1":"4","wrong_answer2":"2","wrong_answer3":"3","correct_answer":"5","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":54,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -9i \\cdot (2 + 8 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-15","wrong_answer2":"-19","wrong_answer3":"-17","correct_answer":"-18","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":55,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -2i \\cdot (3 + 2 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-9","wrong_answer2":"-7","wrong_answer3":"-3","correct_answer":"-6","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":56,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -1i \\cdot (-2 + i)?","wrong_answer1":"4","wrong_answer2":"1","wrong_answer3":"5","correct_answer":"2","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":57,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 9i \\cdot (-10 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-89","wrong_answer2":"-93","wrong_answer3":"-91","correct_answer":"-90","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":58,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = 2i \\cdot (-2 - 3 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-3","wrong_answer2":"-2","wrong_answer3":"-6","correct_answer":"-4","topic":"c","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":59,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -3i \\cdot (2 - 5 i)?","wrong_answer1":"-7","wrong_answer2":"-8","wrong_answer3":"-3","correct_answer":"-6","topic":"c","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":121,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\pi\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"360^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-67.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"157.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-180^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":122,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-247.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-225^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-360^\\circ","correct_answer":"-157.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":123,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-382.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-315^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"67.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"135^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":124,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\pi\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"270^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"135^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-360^\\circ","correct_answer":"-180^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":125,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-337.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-360^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"202.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-157.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":126,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"67.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-337.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-157.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-247.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":127,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{\\pi}{2}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"180^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-382.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-270^\\circ","correct_answer":"90^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":128,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"90^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-22.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-337.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-67.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":129,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"67.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"337.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"315^\\circ","correct_answer":"202.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":130,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{\\pi}{2}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-180^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"225^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"202.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-90^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":131,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"337.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"157.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"292.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-112.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":132,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"315^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-157.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"90^\\circ","correct_answer":"-337.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":133,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{\\pi}{2}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-202.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"67.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-247.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-90^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":134,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"247.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-90^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"157.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"112.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":135,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"180^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-45^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-90^\\circ","correct_answer":"337.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":136,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-135^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-67.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"360^\\circ","correct_answer":"135^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":137,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"360^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"270^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-135^\\circ","correct_answer":"112.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":138,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{3 \\pi}{2}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-112.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"90^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"292.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"270^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":139,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\pi\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-45^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"315^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"270^\\circ","correct_answer":"180^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":140,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"270^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-292.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"292.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"112.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":141,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"225^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-180^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"270^\\circ","correct_answer":"337.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":142,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"292.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-202.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-135^\\circ","correct_answer":"135^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":143,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{\\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-112.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-382.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"225^\\circ","correct_answer":"-22.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":144,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{3 \\pi}{2}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"22.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-135^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"247.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-270^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":145,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\pi\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"135^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-247.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"337.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-180^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":146,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{\\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-382.5^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-180^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-135^\\circ","correct_answer":"22.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":147,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"45^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-315^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"247.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"-247.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":148,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{\\pi}{2}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-180^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-202.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"270^\\circ","correct_answer":"90^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":149,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{\\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"-180^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"67.5^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-247.5^\\circ","correct_answer":"22.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":150,"question":"\\text{Which degree measure corresponds to the radian measure }\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"360^\\circ","wrong_answer2":"-225^\\circ","wrong_answer3":"-45^\\circ","correct_answer":"337.5^\\circ","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":151,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }45^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{9 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"\\pi","correct_answer":"\\frac{\\pi}{4}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":152,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-112.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\pi","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{\\pi}{2}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":153,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }337.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{13 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":154,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-45^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{13 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{\\pi}{4}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":155,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-22.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{\\pi}{4}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{\\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":156,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-337.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{13 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":60,"question":"\\text{What is the imaginary part of } z = -4i \\cdot (-1 + 10 i)?","wrong_answer1":"6","wrong_answer2":"1","wrong_answer3":"2","correct_answer":"4","topic":"c","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":157,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }90^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{2}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{\\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"\\frac{\\pi}{2}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":158,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }157.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","correct_answer":"\\frac{7 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":159,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-315^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{7 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{\\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":160,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-90^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{2}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{11 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{\\pi}{2}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":161,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-67.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\pi","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{\\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{9 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":162,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-67.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":163,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }135^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- 2 \\pi","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{5 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{\\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":164,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-67.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{17 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\pi","wrong_answer3":"2 \\pi","correct_answer":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":165,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-22.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{\\pi}{2}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{\\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":166,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }45^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{2}","correct_answer":"\\frac{\\pi}{4}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":167,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-22.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{9 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{9 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{\\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":168,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }315^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{7 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","correct_answer":"\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":169,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-180^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{\\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","correct_answer":"- \\pi","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":170,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-112.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"2 \\pi","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{2}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":171,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }90^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\pi","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{\\pi}{4}","correct_answer":"\\frac{\\pi}{2}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":172,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-90^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\pi","correct_answer":"- \\frac{\\pi}{2}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":173,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-157.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{5 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{13 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":174,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-135^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"\\pi","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":175,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }135^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"- 2 \\pi","correct_answer":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{4}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":176,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-157.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{5 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{\\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"\\pi","correct_answer":"- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":177,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }247.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{3 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{5 \\pi}{4}","correct_answer":"\\frac{11 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":178,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }90^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{7 \\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{\\pi}{4}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{\\pi}{2}","correct_answer":"\\frac{\\pi}{2}","topic":"r","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":179,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }22.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{7 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{\\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"\\frac{\\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":180,"question":"\\text{Which radian measure corresponds to }-337.5^\\circ\\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"- \\frac{\\pi}{4}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{5 \\pi}{8}","wrong_answer3":"- \\frac{11 \\pi}{8}","correct_answer":"- \\frac{15 \\pi}{8}","topic":"r","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":61,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2 \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{1}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}","correct_answer":"\\text{2x}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":62,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = 3x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{1}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{0}","correct_answer":"\\text{3}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":63,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = 5 \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{1}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{5}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}","correct_answer":"\\text{0}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":64,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^3 \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^3","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2","wrong_answer3":"\\text{3x}","correct_answer":"\\text{3x}^2","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":65,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = e^x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{e}^{x-1}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{xe}^{x-1}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}","correct_answer":"\\text{e}^x","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":66,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\ln(\\text{x}^2)","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{2}{\\text{x}}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}","correct_answer":"\\frac{1}{\\text{x}}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":67,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\sin(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{-sin(x)}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{tan(x)}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{-cos(x)}","correct_answer":"\\text{cos(x)}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":68,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\cos(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{sin(x)}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{cos(x)}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{-cos(x)}","correct_answer":"\\text{-sin(x)}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":69,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x + \\ln(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{1}{\\text{x}}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{1 + x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}","correct_answer":"\\text{1 + }\\frac{1}{\\text{x}}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":70,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2 + 3x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{2x}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x + 3}","correct_answer":"\\text{2x + 3}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":71,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = 2x^2 + 5x + 3 \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{2x + 5}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{4x}","correct_answer":"\\text{4x + 5}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":72,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\tan(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{cot(x)}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{csc}^2(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{sin}^2(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{sec}^2(x)","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":109,"question":"\\text{Using L'Hôpital's Rule, evaluate } \\lim_{x \\to \\infty} \\frac{\\ln(x)}{x} \\text{:}","wrong_answer1":"\\infty","wrong_answer2":"\\text{1}","wrong_answer3":"-1","correct_answer":"\\text{0}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":74,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(x^2) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{1}{x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2x}","correct_answer":"\\frac{2}{x}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":75,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^3 - x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^3 - 1","wrong_answer2":"\\text{3x}^2 + 1","wrong_answer3":"\\text{3x}","correct_answer":"\\text{3x}^2 - 1","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":76,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\frac{1}{x} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{1}{x^2}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{-1}{x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}^{-1}","correct_answer":"\\frac{-1}{x^2}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":77,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2 + \\cos(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x + cos(x)}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2 - \\sin(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2x + cos(x)}","correct_answer":"\\text{2x - sin(x)}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":78,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\sin^2(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{cos(x)}","wrong_answer2":"\\sin(2x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{sin(x)}","correct_answer":"\\text{2sin(x)cos(x)}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":79,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = 1 + x^2 \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2}","correct_answer":"\\text{2x}","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":80,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^3 + e^x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^3e^x","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^3 + e^{x+1}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{3x}^2 - e^x","correct_answer":"\\text{3x}^2 + e^x","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":81,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^3 + \\ln(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^3 + \\ln(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\text{3x} + \\ln(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{3x}^2 + \\ln(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{3x}^2 + \\frac{1}{x}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":82,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = e^{2x} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2e^x","wrong_answer2":"\\text{e}^{2x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2x}","correct_answer":"\\text{2e}^{2x}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":83,"question":"\\text{Using the chain rule, what is the derivative of } f(x) = \\sin(2x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\cos(2x)","wrong_answer2":"\\text{-cos(2x)}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{-2sin(2x)}","correct_answer":"\\text{2cos(2x)}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":84,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(x^2 + 1) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{1}{x^2 + 1}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2 + 1","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{x}{x^2 + 1}","correct_answer":"\\frac{2x}{x^2 + 1}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":85,"question":"\\text{Using the product rule, what is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2e^x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2 + e^x","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2e^x","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2x} + e^x","correct_answer":"\\text{x}^2e^x + 2xe^x","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":86,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2\\sin(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2\\cos(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}\\cos(x) + \\sin(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2x} + \\sin(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{2x}\\sin(x) + \\text{x}^2\\cos(x)","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":87,"question":"\\text{Using the quotient rule, what is the derivative of } f(x) = \\frac{x}{x+1} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{x}{x^2}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{1}{x+1} - \\frac{x}{(x+1)^2}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{x}{x+1}","correct_answer":"\\frac{1}{(x+1)^2}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":88,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = e^{\\sin(x)} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{sin(x)e}^{\\cos(x)}","wrong_answer2":"\\cos(x)e^{\\sin(x)}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{e}^{\\cos(x)}\\sin(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{e}^{\\sin(x)}\\cos(x)","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":89,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\cos^2(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{cos}^2(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\text{-sin}^2(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2cos(x)sin(x)}","correct_answer":"\\text{-2cos(x)sin(x)}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":90,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(x)\\sin(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\cos(x) + \\ln(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\ln(x)\\cos(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{\\sin(x)}{x}","correct_answer":"\\cos(x)\\ln(x) + \\frac{\\sin(x)}{x}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":91,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\sqrt{x^2 + 1} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{2x}{\\sqrt{x^2 + 1}}","wrong_answer2":"\\sqrt{x^2 + 1}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{1}{x^2 + 1}","correct_answer":"\\frac{x}{\\sqrt{x^2 + 1}}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":92,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(\\cos(x)) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\sec(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\tan(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{-cos(x)}","correct_answer":"\\text{-tan(x)}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":93,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^5 - 2x^3 + x^2 \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{5x}^4 - 6x^3 + x^2","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^5 + x^2","wrong_answer3":"\\text{5x}^4 - 6x^2","correct_answer":"\\text{5x}^4 - 6x^2 + 2x","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":94,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(x^3) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{3x}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{1}{x}","correct_answer":"\\frac{3}{x}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":95,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^3 + 2e^x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{2x} + e^x","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2 + 2e^x","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}^3 + e^x","correct_answer":"\\text{3x}^2 + 2e^x","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":96,"question":"\\text{Using the quotient rule, what is the derivative of } f(x) = \\frac{x^3}{e^x} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{x^3 - 3x^2}{e^x}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{x^2 - x^3}{e^x}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{x^3}{e^x}","correct_answer":"\\frac{3x^2 - x^3}{e^x}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":98,"question":"\\text{What is the second derivative of } f(x) = e^{x^2} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{2e}^{x^2} + 2xe^{x^2}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{2xe}^{x^2}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{4x}^2e^{x^2}","correct_answer":"\\text{4x}^2e^{x^2} + 2e^{x^2}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":99,"question":"\\text{Using L'Hôpital's Rule, evaluate } \\lim_{x \\to 0} \\frac{e^x - 1}{x} \\text{:}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{e}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{-1}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{0}","correct_answer":"\\text{1}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":100,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(\\tan(x)) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\tan(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\sec^2(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\csc^2(x)","correct_answer":"\\frac{\\sec^2(x)}{\\tan(x)}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":101,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^3\\ln(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^3 + 3x","wrong_answer2":"\\text{3x}^2 + \\ln(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}^2 + \\ln(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{3x}^2\\ln(x) + \\text{x}^2","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":102,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^4e^{-x} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^4e^{-x} + 4x^3e^{-x}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^3e^{-x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{4x}^3e^{-x} + \\text{x}^4e^{-x}","correct_answer":"\\text{4x}^3e^{-x} - \\text{x}^4e^{-x}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":103,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\sqrt{\\tan(x)} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{\\sec(x)}{2\\sqrt{\\tan(x)}}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{1}{\\tan(x)\\sqrt{x}}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{1}{\\sec(x)\\sqrt{\\tan(x)}}","correct_answer":"\\frac{\\sec^2(x)}{2\\sqrt{\\tan(x)}}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":104,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(x^2 + 3x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{x + 3}{x^2 + 3x}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{x}{x^2 + 3x}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{2x}{x^2 + 3x}","correct_answer":"\\frac{2x + 3}{x^2 + 3x}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":105,"question":"\\text{What is the second derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{1}{x}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{1}{x^2}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{-1}{x}","correct_answer":"\\frac{-1}{x^2}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":106,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2\\cos(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2\\sin(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\text{2x}\\cos(x) + \\text{x}^2\\sin(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}^2\\cos(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{2x}\\cos(x) - \\text{x}^2\\sin(x)","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":107,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = e^{\\sin(x^2)} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{e}^{x^2}\\cos(x^2)","wrong_answer2":"\\text{e}^{\\cos(x^2)}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{e}^{\\sin(x^2)}\\cos(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{2x}e^{\\sin(x^2)}\\cos(x^2)","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":108,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\frac{\\ln(x)}{x} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{\\ln(x)}{x^2}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{1}{x}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{\\ln(x) - 1}{x^2}","correct_answer":"\\frac{1 - \\ln(x)}{x^2}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":110,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2\\ln(x^2) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}\\ln(x^2) + \\text{2x}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2 + \\text{2ln(x)}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2x}\\ln(x) + \\text{x}^2","correct_answer":"\\text{2x}\\ln(x^2) + \\text{2x}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":97,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\sin^3(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\sin^2(x)\\cos(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\cos^3(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{3cos}^2(x)\\sin(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{3sin}^2(x)\\cos(x)","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":111,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\cot^2(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\cot(x)\\csc^2(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\text{2cot(x)csc}^2(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{-csc}^2(x)","correct_answer":"\\text{-2cot(x)csc}^2(x)","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":112,"question":"\\text{What is the second derivative of } f(x) = x^2e^x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2e^x + 2xe^x","wrong_answer2":"\\text{2x} + e^x","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}^2 + 2e^x","correct_answer":"\\text{x}^2e^x + 4xe^x + 2e^x","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":113,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\sqrt{\\ln(x)} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{1}{x\\ln(x)}","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{\\ln(x)}{x^2}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{1}{\\ln(x)}","correct_answer":"\\frac{1}{2x\\sqrt{\\ln(x)}}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":114,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = e^x\\sin(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\sin(x) + e^x","wrong_answer2":"\\text{e}^x\\cos(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\cos(x)e^x","correct_answer":"\\text{e}^x(\\sin(x) + \\cos(x))","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":115,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(\\sqrt{x^2 + 1}) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\ln(x^2 + 1)","wrong_answer2":"\\frac{2x}{x^2 + 1}","wrong_answer3":"\\frac{1}{x^2 + 1}","correct_answer":"\\frac{x}{x^2 + 1}","topic":"d","difficulty":3,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":116,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2 \\ln(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2 + \\ln(x)","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x} + 2x\\ln(x)","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}^2\\ln(x) + x","correct_answer":"\\text{2x}\\ln(x) + x","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":117,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = e^{x^2} \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{e}^{x^2}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{2x}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{x}^2e^x","correct_answer":"\\text{2x}e^{x^2}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":120,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x\\cos(x) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{-xsin(x)}","wrong_answer2":"\\text{xcos(x) - sin(x)}","wrong_answer3":"\\text{-cos(x) + xsin(x)}","correct_answer":"\\cos(x) - x\\sin(x)","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":73,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = x^2e^x \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\text{x}^2 + e^x","wrong_answer2":"\\text{x}^2e^x","wrong_answer3":"\\text{2x + e}^x","correct_answer":"\\text{x}^2e^x + 2xe^x","topic":"d","difficulty":1,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60},{"task_id":119,"question":"\\text{What is the derivative of } f(x) = \\ln(1 + x^2) \\text{?}","wrong_answer1":"\\frac{1}{1 + x^2}","wrong_answer2":"\\ln(x^2)","wrong_answer3":"\\ln(x)","correct_answer":"\\frac{2x}{1 + x^2}","topic":"d","difficulty":2,"points":10,"status":"a","user_id":60}]